Here is my readme file for project 1. I am using Python3.6 Opencv3.3


plot_ols.py is my linear regression function

my_brown.py my_red.py my_notbred.py my_notyellow are used to extract color data function

g_data includes gaussian mixture mean, covariance, probability, and segmentation picture algarithm

find_color includes myAlgorithm which is used to find the red region and draw bounding box etc.

my toplevel is my top level code which is used to test my code.

